o ISBN Pierre
To the sea where my father
is, the future Bonnie chooses!
"To the Sea Where My Father is!
The Future Bonney Chooses"
Three
Years Ago,
Mt. Corvo,
Goa Kingdom,
East Blue
Oh, gross!
Now come Kuma!
Battle!
Ahhhh!
Well, how'd you like that one?
Don't worry, I'm not going
to use it on you guys.
I'm ready.
With moves like these, no
one in the world can beat me.
Monkey D. Luffy (Age 16)
I bet I could even take ace.
Dragon.
You seem rather familiar
with this country.
Why did you go to that village
on its outskirts to see someone?
You were watching that boy, but
you never said a word to him.
Keep talking and it'll be the death of me.
Why is that?
A child is every parent's weak spot.
Sorry, I'll let it go.
Forgive me.
It's my special move!
No one can stand up to that one!
It's a big deal.
So I'll save it for when I gotta
fight someone really tough.
When I'm a pirate, I'm going
to have a crew, of course.
But one of them might get beaten
up and captured by the enemy.
Then I'll say, not so fast, jerk.
Nobody messes with my crew.
So come go, battle axe. Huh?
Still scared?
It's OK, guys.
I don't eat cowards.
Hey, who's there?
It was weird. I felt something.
It gave me a chill.
Some wild animal must be king
of the mountain here, huh?
I'll find him.
Pirates attacked a merchant ship and fled.
Chase them down while they're close.
Who are you?
I'm here to help you.
Are you the merchants who were
raided by pirates just now?
They showed up out of
nowhere and took our cargo.
And can you take care of the fire?
It looks bad, but we can
handle it, no problem.
I'm not gonna make it.
Please don't say that. Hang in there.
Wait here.
I'll transport him to a hospital.
Hurry up and move, Kuma!
What are you doing?
Chase down that pirate ship!
I'll have your cargo back
by the time you catch up.
We'll be on our way soon. Thank you.
You're a hero.
No! No!
It's Bartholomew Goomba!
Surrender immediately. Aye aye, sir!
Grab the cargo and bring
it in before he kills us!
Dear Bonnie...
The world's beauty can't be captured by
drawings or photos and encyclopedias.
It's brimming with exquisite scenery!
I can't wait to watch your
face light up when you see it.
Sorbet Kingdom
I'm sure your dad is just busy traveling,
or maybe the news coup got lost.
But he said he'd write me, and
I haven't gotten one letter.
The more you want them,
the slower time will go.
Be patient, dear.
They'll come soon enough.
Oh.
Oh!
Hello?
The newspaper.
And a letter.
Put this in the mailbox.
Yes, ma 'am.
A letter?
No, sorry.
It's just the paper.
Another letter came today.
Yes.
How many are we up to?
He's been sending her
about 10 letters a month.
It's been dozens by now.
How can one idiot have
so much to write about?
Dear Bonnie.
Get the shit!
And Bonney, though I've said
it countless times, I love you.
All right, Pert, your turn.
What's wrong, Bonney?
Kyokyo?
Mommy!
Oh, come on, not again.
Hey, want to play Jango? No!
I want to play!
You little freak!
Bonnie, turn back to normal. Hurry!
It's time to take your medicine, Bonnie.
She's so lucky to have a
hard-working nurse like you.
Care for a cup of tea?
No, I'm...
I'm fine, thank you.
That's strange.
Was I seeing things?
Bonnie looked like some
sort of hulking brute.
Here, open wide!
Whoa, it's all better! I hate it!
I know, sweetie, but it's good for you.
Actually, it's just a bitter placebo.
I'm confused, Connie.
Why do we have to keep Bonnie's
powers a secret from her?
Better to be safe, I say.
Besides, haven't you heard that
a wise wolf hides its fangs?
Marines' Science
Group, Laboratory 8
That's incredible, doctor!
It's complete already!
Indeed, all that's left is to lift my
lab and my brain with island clouds.
Most of the buildings you
see here are holograms.
I had intended to do this on Punk
Hazard originally, like the head cut.
By the way, I feel so light.
I could not for me.
Poor Kuma.
They're really going to
take your free will away.
Hmm.
A clone with free will
and a human without it.
Which one of us has it worse?
Don't say that.
To see, you're perfectly human.
So when I lose my will,
what will that mean?
Well, for example, you
say you follow orders now.
But what if the government
ordered you to kill a child?
You would resist. Yes.
This experiment will strip side
away your memories as a human,
and thus your human emotions will no...
longer exist.
The exam is done.
You're free to go now. Looking good.
What's it like?
Starting to feel anxious?
I'm fine.
I'm not worried about myself.
I
don't believe that for an instant.
You'll lose your memories and emotions.
No one can simply accept that.
You couldn't.
Not when there's someone you love.
Remember, until this is over, I'll ensure
that you retain some free will, at least.
You have roughly a year
till then, so don't worry.
Writing her another letter?
I have to send as many as
I can while I have time.
To tell Bonnie I love her.
Over the next year, I'm going to write
down a lifetime's worth of feelings.
That's so sweet!
I can't believe she's
about to turn nine already.
I bet she's grown so much.
It hasn't been that long.
I don't know when this letter
will reach you, Bonnie.
But happy ninth birthday.
I'm at Vegapunk's lab now.
And...
Mommy, happy birthday!
We love you.
Grandma, Connie made her special
giant pizza for you! Yay!
Thank you!
So good?
Nothing.
Still no letter.
Be patient, dear.
They'll come soon enough.
It was my birthday today.
Dad, you promised you'd write me.
Baltigo, Revolutionary
Army Headquarters
So Kuma saved our forces again. Yes, sir.
We were in a bad spot
till he bailed us out.
Kuma
But he left without saying a word.
Just like before.
If that's what he wants,
then fine, let him go.
He must have a reason for it.
One that he can't tell us.
I'm killed! See? See?
All the stones are gone!
Oh, I'm so happy for you.
You've been a very patient girl.
I can go outside now!
Not so fast.
I'm still here.
I'm supposed to take care of
you until your 10th birthday.
And that's just what I'm going to do.
You're a liar!
You can't trick me!
Vegapunk told me I'd be all better in
a year, and it's been longer than that!
You can't leave.
I'm not sick anymore!
Leave me alone!
Too bad for you.
That nurse is terrible.
How could she do this to her?
I have news.
Alpha and her teammates are
government intelligence agents.
She's not a nurse, but
how can that pass? Shhh!
Here's what I've heard.
She was getting drunk in town the
other day and kept running her mouth.
Turns out you were right, Bonnie.
She told people you were completely cured.
She said that?
I don't know what she's cooking up,
but it's too fishy for my taste.
Why would she want to keep someone who's
perfectly healthy cooped up for six months?
It's also strange that you haven't
gotten a single letter from Kuma,
don't you think?
I've already talked with
Gyogyo and the others.
Make for the port.
Hurry, they'll take you to sea.
And you can search for your father.
You think we'll find him?
Don't worry.
You'll see him soon.
You're leaving?
Yes, returning to the palace.
Fine. Take care.
Yokyo and his friends
are no ordinary fishable.
Even pirates and sea monsters cower
at the mention of their names.
With them on your side,
I know you'll find Kuma.
I made it outside.
There's dirt.
And rain.
The grass!
The sky!
The sun!
Bonnie's actually walking outside.
It's a miracle.
There really is a god.
I said sail!
Bonnie!
Over here!
Yuckoo! Toto! Potato!
Look! Look!
I made it outside!
Where's Bonney hiding?
Queen Dowager Connie?
But you just went out a moment ago!
What's going on here?
I'm Bonnie!
The hell you are! Neat, huh?
I made the ship look like pizza!
I love it!
Fool me, will you?
You'll pay for this!
And away we go!
Not so fast!
It's Alpha!
We gotta move!
She's coming!
If the subject tries to escape, then
nothing is off the table anymore!
I'll subdue you by any means necessary!
That'll make this so much easier! What?
She's a government agent!
She uses the six powers!
I can't keep going now.
Not like this.
I can't kill Bonnie.
But I can kill the rest!
I can't.
I can't go back.
Dad.
What should I do?
Hey, Dad, can you tell
me what Nico looks like?
Unfortunately, no one
knows for sure, but...
Nico!
DISTORTING Denjiro!
You could transform!
I knew it was you! Morley!
But they say his body could
move and stretch like rubber.
He fought fast and free,
flying however he fancied.
Miserable brat!
Niko's like future!
Bonnie's escape was immediately
reported to the World Government.
and she set out with the
fishermen in search of her father.
They would soon evolve
into a new era pirate crew,
rivaling even the Straw Hats in infamy.
What do you want?
I need a message. I need a message.
All of them are here.
I can't wait.
The voice of my voice is my turn.
I'm deaf.
I'm deaf. I'm deaf.
You can't listen to me.
You can't hear me.
I don't have to eat, but
the deep sea is shining.
Every day, we're not going to die.
We're not going to die here.
It's so different.
Come on.
We're not going to die.
Look at this door, now I'll give up.
Don't let me go, I'm not the girl.
Don't let her out.
Check all the way.
I ask the state.
Why don't you go beyond the day?
And I think that it's one of the
main things. Why don't you know?
You